Szappanos Tamás Soma

Personal Details

Síp u. 15., 6090 Kunszentmiklós 12.23.1997., Budapest, Hungary Phone number: +36209898428 E-mail: szppply@gmail.com



About me

With my studies, computer and communication skills I would like to support the company's operations and its progress. I honestly believe that this position would give me an opportunity to accomplish these and develop myself. As I am hardworking, reliable and have the relevant skills and experience needed to succeed in this job, I hope that my application will be considered.

Employment history

September 2020 – November 2020 BP Business Service Centre Kft.

Financial Accountant

Perform controlling, financial and accounting tasks and processes for different regions.

September 2019 – September 2020 BP Business Service Centre Kft.

Finance & Accounting Intern

Assisting in financial, accounting and bookkeeping processes with the daily use of SAP, Excel and Power BI.

August 2019 – September 2019 Sziget Cultural Management Ltd., Budapest

June 2018 – September 2018 Ticket Sales Coordinator

Segmentation, control and execution of ticket distribution tasks on behalf of Sziget Cultural Management Ltd.

Education

September 2016 – June 2020 Budapest Business School Faculty of Finance and

Accounting, Budapest

Business Informatics BSc

Thesis title: Digitalization and Automation for a Business

Service Centre

September 2008 – June 2016 Baksay Sándor Calvinistic High School, Kunszentmiklós

High School Diploma

I graduated from high school with A grades.

Skills

IT Microsoft Office, SAP, Power BI, Tableau, SQL, HTML, CSS, Java,

Wordpress, SPSS, IBM Watson Analytics

Languages English (B2)

Additional knowledge Database Management, Data Analysis, Data Visualisation, Business

Intelligence (BI), IT, Mathematics, Accounting, Finance, Statistics

Hobbies

Sport has always been an important thing in my life. I have been playing professional basketball since I was 14 years old and currently I am a point guard in Miklósi KékRókák. Moreover, I also play football and tennis occasionally. I am into listening to music, reading books, and interested in watching films.

Budapest, 2020. 11. 23.